{
    "subject": "resource/Heorhiy_Narbut",
    "predicate": "ontology/training",
    "object": "resource/Simon_Holl\u00f3sy",
    "human_readable": "Heorhiy Narbut was trained by Simon Holl\u00f3sy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9757754802703857,
            "question": "What kind of training did Heorhiy Narbut receive from Simon Holl\u00f3sy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9440087676048279,
            "question": "Who trained Heorhiy Narbut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967412114143372,
            "question": "How does the training under Simon Holl\u00f3sy potentially influence Heorhiy Narbut's artistic development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8906303644180298,
            "question": "What is the profession of Simon Holl\u00f3sy, considering his role in Heorhiy Narbut's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8881627321243286,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Heorhiy Narbut and Simon Holl\u00f3sy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8648160696029663,
            "question": "Can you describe the mentorship dynamic between Heorhiy Narbut and Simon Holl\u00f3sy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8527039289474487,
            "question": "To whom did Heorhiy Narbut owe his training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7790547013282776,
            "question": "Who was responsible for educating Heorhiy Narbut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5238668918609619,
            "question": "Name the teacher of Heorhiy Narbut."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4269607961177826,
            "question": "Based on this relationship, what can you infer about the artistic style or approach of Heorhiy Narbut?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Heorhiy Narbut was trained by Simon Holl\u00f3sy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7595_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the teacher of Heorhiy Narbut.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7595_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was responsible for educating Heorhiy Narbut?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7595_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Heorhiy Narbut owe his training?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7595_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7595_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while there are multiple documents mentioning Heorhiy Narbut's education and training, none of them mention Simon Holl\u00f3sy as his trainer. In fact, one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7595/re-ranker-msmarco/35.txt) mentions that Narbut continued some of his studies in Munich, in the school of Simon Holl\u00f3sy, but it also states that he studied with painters Ivan Bilibin and Mstislav Dobuzhinsky. This suggests that Holl\u00f3sy was not a direct trainer or educator of Narbut's, but rather a school where Narbut continued his studies at some point."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Heorhiy Narbut studied with painters Ivan Bilibin and Mstislav Dobuzhinsky, and also mentions he continued some of his studies in Munich under the school of Simon Holl\u00f3sy. This supports the statement that Heorhiy Narbut was trained by Simon Holl\u00f3sy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "the text states \"Narbut continued some of his studies in Munich, in the school of Simon Holl\u00f3sy.\" which implies that Narbut did not study directly under Holl\u00f3sy.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}